Guide to the George Breitman Papers TAM.169
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series V: Lists and Indexes
  - The Militant- articles by George Lavan & James Thayer, 1947-1976, list of, undated (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - The Militant articles - GLW (George Weissman?), FL (Frank Lovell), GL (George Lavan), JTC (James Thayer), GB (George Breitman), 1946-1969, list of, undated (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - New Militant: index v. 1& 2, Dec 15, 1934-Jun 6, 1936, undated (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Pseudonyms (compiled by Pierre Broue), undated (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Pseudonyms, Liste des, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Socialist Appeal(Chicago): articles list, v. 1-3, 1935-1937, undated (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Socialist Appeal(New York): index 1:1-20, Aug 14-Dec 25, 1937 [by subject, country, author], undated (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Socialist Appeal, 1938: list of articles, undated (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Socialist Appeal: index, Jan-Jul 1939 [by author, country, subject], undated (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Socialist Appeal, Jul-Dec 1939 - contents list, author index, undated (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Socialist Workers Party: contents lists for Internal Bulletins, 1939-1981, undated (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Socialist Workers Party (WWII era) - pseudonyms, undated (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Trotsky: a chronological list of Leon Trotsky published writings, 1929-1940, Pathfinder Press, undated (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Women's Liberation: writings in the SWP press, undated (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Young Spartacus: articles list, 1931-1935, undated (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Series VI. Addendum (Unprocessed)
  - Unprocessed Materials (May be or contain Duplicates), undated (Box 64)
  - Unprocessed Materials (May be or contain Duplicates), undated (Box 65)
  - Unprocessed Materials (May be or contain duplicates): Minutes; Various Committees, undated (Box 66)
  - Unprocessed Materials (May be or contain Duplicates): Memos; Circular Letters, undated (Box 67)